fantasticcontraption.com 2012-09-19

# Fantastic Contraption: A fun online physics puzzle game

## Privacy Policy, Terms & Conditions

_Last updated 1/14/09_

**Privacy Policy**

This page represents inXile Entertainment Inc.'s ("inXile") privacy policy and the terms of use for the Fantastic Contraption game found on this website (the "Game") and for website (the "Site"). inXile takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy and terms of use. By using the Site you are accepting these terms.

NOTICE: Click [here](http://www.onguardonline.gov/default.aspx) for practical tips from the federal government and the technology industry to help you guard against Internet fraud, secure your computer and protect your personal information.

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This policy covers how inXile treats personal information that it collects and receives through the Site. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that inXile does not own or control, or to people that inXile does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**

**General**

inXile collects personal information when you register with the Site, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes that may be offered by inXile on the Site. inXile may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies or public sources.

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, ZIP code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. When you register with the Site and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

inXile automatically receives and records from cookies inXile may place on your computer non-Personally Identifiable Information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the pages you request.

inXile uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with promotions or sweepstakes, keep you informed about products and services that may interest you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

**Children**

The Site is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information (PII) from children under 13 years of age beyond an e-mail address used only once for verification purposes. While children under the age of 13 can create/save designs, they are not permitted to post in the forums. We strongly encourage parents to review the Privacy Policies and Terms of Use of these other sites before allowing your children to view them. 

If you are a child under the age of 13, the email address we collect from you during the registration process will be deleted from our records immediately following the verification process, and we will not use the email address to contact you or share it with any third parties.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

inXile does not rent, sell, or share personal information collected from the Site about you with non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

-We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with inXile under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help inXile communicate with you about offers from the Site and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

-We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

-We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of inXile's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

-We transfer information about you if inXile is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, inXile will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Links**

The Site may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by inXile from the Site.

**Third Party Advertising**

The Site may display targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria- for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.

inXile does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the advertisement.

Advertisements that appear on the Site are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. inXile does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on the Site unless you choose to share it with them.

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by inXile and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

The Site's advertisers may include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies).

**Changing or Removing Information**

Access and control over most personal information on the Site is readily available through the profile editing tools. You may modify or delete any of your profile information at any time by logging into your account. Information will be updated immediately. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to members of the Site.

Where you make use of the communication features of the service to share information with other individuals on the Site, however, (e.g., sending a personal message to another user on the Site) you generally cannot remove such communications.

**Ownership and Use**

Fantastic Contraption is a trademark of inXile Entertainment, Inc. All information, content, services and software displayed on, transmitted through, or used in connection with the Site and the Game, including for example guides, text, images, illustrations, audio clips, video, html, source and object code, trademarks, logos, and the like, and all associated goodwill (collectively, the "Content"), is owned by or used under license by inXile. You may configure and create unique levels of the Game using the Game's Content, but no other use is permitted without prior written permission of inXile. For example, you may not republish or redistribute any portion of the Content in any form of media, whether or not for payment or other consideration, or incorporate the Content in any derivative, compilation, archive or cache, other than your configuration of your levels of the Game. Modification, copying, framing, caching, reproducing, selling, publishing, transmitting, displaying or otherwise using any portion of the Content for purposes other than configuring your tracks is prohibited without the express prior written authorization of inXile. Don't steal the Game. If you would like to host it on your site, create a link to [http://www.fantasticcontraption.com](http://www.fantasticcontraption.com/) for fans to play the Game. inXile does not authorize anyone to host the Game on their site without prior consent. 

**Changes to These Terms**

inXile may occasionally make changes to these terms. If we post changes to these terms, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of these terms. Your use of the Site after any posted and effected change will be deemed an acceptance of such change.

**Miscellaneous**

These terms are governed exclusively by the laws of the State of California, without reference to its conflict of laws principles or the United Nations Convention on the International Sale of Goods. The parties hereby submit to the exclusive personal jurisdiction of, and agree that any controversy,claim or legal proceeding with respect to or arising under these terms or the use of the Site shall be brought in the State or Federal Courts residing in Orange County, California. The Site and the Game are provided on an "AS IS" and "AS AVAILABLE" basis. inXile is not responsible for any damages that may arise from your use of the Site or the Game.  
If you have any questions regarding these terms, you may contact us at inXile Entertainment, Inc. 2727 Newport Blvd, Suite 100, Newport Beach, CA 92626 Attn: Fantastic Contraption
